https://www.johnstonmurphy.com/privacy-policy.html

TERMS OF USE
Welcome to the Johnston & Murphy Web Site ("Site"). The "Site" is owned and controlled by Genesco Inc. ("Genesco", "We", or "Us"). Please review the following basic rules that govern your use of our Site (the "Agreement"). Please note that your use of our Site means that you agree to those rules.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: September 15, 2020.
CHANGES IN PRIVACY POLICY
We may from time to time change these rules. We will notify users of the site of any changes by posting the revised policy reflecting them with a new effective date on this page. Your use of our Site following any such change means that you agree to the rules as changed. These rules--specifically including the "Privacy and Customer Information Policy" below--apply to this website only and not to any other website or business activity of Genesco, Johnston & Murphy or any other division of Genesco.
PRIVACY AND CUSTOMER INFORMATION POLICY
Data Collection: We currently collect the categories of personal information listed in the “Categories of Personal Information We Collect” section below, and we may use the data for the purposes identified for in the “Purposes for which Categories Will Be Used” section below.   As permitted by applicable law, we may use and disclose all of the personal information that we collect in order to:
Comply with federal, state, or local laws;
Comply with a civil, criminal, or regulatory inquiry, investigation, subpoena, or summons by federal, state, or local authorities;
Cooperate with law enforcement agencies concerning conduct or activity that we, a service provider, or a third party reasonably and in good faith believe may violate federal, state, or local law;
Exercise or defend legal claims; and
Collect, use, retain, sell, or disclose consumer information that is deidentified or in the aggregate consumer information.
Categories of Personal Information We Collect:  We collect the following categories of personal information:
Identifiers, this includes, real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier Internet Protocol (IP) address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers
Categories of personal information described in California’s data breach notification law, this includes, name, signature, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, education, employment, employment history, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information
Protected classifications under California or federal law, this includes, birthdate/age or gender
Commercial information, this includes, records of personal property, products or services (work, labor, and services, including services furnished in connection with the sale or repair of goods) purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
Internet or other electronic network activity information, this includes, browsing history; search history; internet service provider (ISP); type of computer; type of web browser; URLs of any referring or exited webpages; operating system; information about your interaction with the Site or advertisements on it; data about which pages you visit; the date and time of your visit; your domain server; and your browser type
If you receive email communications from us, we may use certain tools to capture data related to if/when you open our message and if/when you click on any links or banners it contains.  Other information collected through this email tracking feature includes:  your email address, the date and time of your “click” on the email, a message number, the name of the list from which the message was sent, a tracking URL number, and a destination page.
When you engage with any of the social media platforms under our management, or the management of our corporate subsidiaries and affiliates, we will collect and aggregate the personal information that is tied to your account (for example, your name, username, email address, and location) and your engagement with us, including all content, messages, and information that you provide to us.  [We may also utilize a chatbot when responding to direct messages from you.]
Please see the “Cookies and Similar Technologies” section of this Policy for more information, including information about the specific technologies in use.
Geolocation data, this includes, location data automatically collected during use of the Site; location data provided when locating stores; shipping and billing address; [beacons; geofencing; geotargeting]
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information, this includes, call center recordings and electronic communications with us
Interences, this includes, derivation of information, data, assumptions, or conclusions from facts, evidence, or another source of information or data) drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes
Purposes for which Categories Will Be Used: We use the categories of personal information identified above to:
Process your purchases and returns
Process your payments and refunds;
Detect fraud and prevent loss;
Provide you with catalogs and information about our products and services;
Contact you about products or services that may be of interest to you;
Enable you to track the status of your purchase or return;
Establish and maintain your user account with us;
Manage our relationship with you;
Allow you to contact us and facilitate your communication with us;
Respond to your feedback, requests, questions, or inquiries;
Register you for our email or text message distribution lists;
Send you periodic emails or text messages;
Administer a contest, sweepstakes, promotion, or survey;
Administer our birthday club rewards program;
Enable you to share reviews, comments, questions, and answers and to show you as a verified buyer;
Provide you more tailored advertising;
Operate the Site and prepare aggregate traffic information (which we may share with our affiliates and advertisers);
Recognize your browser/device and remember your preferences and interactions
Operate, enable, and improve the Site and its content/functionality;
Understand how you interact with the Site and enhance your experience on the Site by providing a more personal and interactive experience;
Track visits to the Site and usage analytics (e.g. page response times, download errors, length of visit, webpages visited, etc.);
Manage and maintain the security of the Site;
Provide notice of changes to the Site or the services we offer or provide through it;
Conduct research and analysis and improve our products and marketing efforts;
Determine and track customer interests, needs, and preferences;
Engage with you on social media;
Operate our business;
Develop new products and services;
Improve our customer service;
Maintain insurance for our business;
Maintain our inventory records and perform our accounting and audit functions;
Facilitate corporate mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, dissolutions, or other transfers;
Ensure safety of person or property; and
Ask if you would like for us to share your information with third parties.
Additional Data Collection and Uses: We will not collect categories of personal information other than those disclosed above without providing a new notice at collection. In addition, we will not use your personal information for any purpose other than those disclosed above. If we intend to use your personal information for a purpose that was not previously disclosed in the notice at collection, we will directly notify you of the new use and obtain consent from you to use it for the new purpose.
Is entry of personal information required? You may choose not to provide us with personal information, but you will not be able to access portions of the Site that require your personal information (such as completing online orders). Some pages of the Site, including our online forms and applications, may give you the option of providing certain of your personal information. If you want to change or update any information about yourself that you have submitted, you may contact us via the contact methods listed at the end of this Policy.
PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION DURING LAST 12 MONTHS
Personal Information Collected: We have collected the categories of personal information listed below during the preceding 12 months, and we used that data for the purposes identified under each category.
Identifiers
Categories of personal information described in California’s data breach notification law
Protected classifications under California or federal law
Commercial information
Internet or other electronic network activity information
Geolocation data
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
Inferences
Categories of Sources: You, the consumer, and [governmental entities/public records; data resellers]; [Data enrichment vendors who assist with our marketing efforts].
Business and Commercial Purposes for Collecting: We use the categories of personal information identified above to:
Process your purchases and returns;
Process your payments and refunds;
Detect fraud and prevent loss;
Provide you with catalogs and information about our products and services;
Contact you about products or services that may be of interest to you;
Enable you to track the status of your purchase or return;
Establish and maintain your user account with us;
Manage our relationship with you;
Allow you to contact us and facilitate your communication with us;
Respond to your feedback, requests, questions, or inquiries;
Register you for our email or text message distribution lists;
Send you periodic emails or text messages;
Administer a contest, sweepstakes, promotion, or survey;
Administer our birthday club rewards program;
Enable you to share reviews, comments, questions, and answers and to show you as a verified buyer;
Provide you more tailored advertising;
Operate the Site and prepare aggregate traffic information (which we may share with our affiliates and advertisers);
Recognize your browser/device and remember your preferences and interactions
Operate, enable, and improve the Site and its content/functionality;
Understand how you interact with the Site and enhance your experience on the Site by providing a more personal and interactive experience;
Track visits to the Site and usage analytics (e.g. page response times, download errors, length of visit, webpages visited, etc.);
Manage and maintain the security of the Site;
Provide notice of changes to the Site or the services we offer or provide through it;
Conduct research and analysis and improve our products and marketing efforts;
Determine and track customer interests, needs, and preferences;
Engage with you on social media;
Operate our business;
Develop new products and services;
Improve our customer service;
Maintain insurance for our business;
Maintain our inventory records and perform our accounting and audit functions;
Facilitate corporate mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, dissolutions, or other transfers;
Ensure safety of person or property; and
Ask if you would like for us to share your information with third parties.
Categories of third parties with whom we share personal information:  We have shared each category of personal information with the following categories of third parties:
Subsidiaries and affiliates
Service providers (e.g. accounts, attorneys, advisors, mailing, marketing, shipping fulfillment, payment processing, Site administration, technical support, modeling, analytics
Data enrichment vendors who assist with our marketing efforts
Personal Information Shared with Third Party Marketing Partners: We do not transfer your Personal Information in exchange for money, but information may have been shared with certain third-party marketing partners. Specifically, limited identifying information may have been shared with such partners. Under the California Consumer Privacy Act, California residents may be entitled to opt-out of such sharing, referred to as a “Do Not Sell” right.  We may have shared the following categories of personal information with such partners described above during the preceding 12 months:
Identifiers
Categories of personal information described in California’s data breach notification law
Protected classifications under California or federal law
Commercial information
Internet or other electronic network activity information
Geolocation data
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
Inferences
Personal Information Disclosed for a Business Purpose: We have disclosed for a business purpose the categories of personal information listed below during the preceding 12 months:
Identifiers
Categories of personal information described in California’s data breach notification law
Protected classifications under California or federal law
Commercial information
Internet or other electronic network activity information
Geolocation data
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
Inferences
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides California residents with the additional rights listed below. To exercise these rights see the “Exercising Your California Privacy Rights” section or visit our Privacy Portal.
Right to opt out of Sale of Personal Information. Where provided by law, you have the right to direct us to stop selling your personal information to third parties and refrain from doing so in the future.
As noted above, we share Personal Information with business partners for joint marketing initiatives. That sharing may constitute a “sale” under California law, even though we do not receive monetary payment for sharing. If you opt-out, going forward, we will not share your information with such third parties to use for such purposes unless you later direct us to do so.
Right to Know. You have the right to know and see what data we have collected about you over the past 12 months, including:
The categories of personal information we have collected about you;
The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected;
The business or commercial purpose for collecting your personal information;
The categories of third parties with whom we have shared your personal information; and
The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.
Right to Delete. You have the right to request that we delete the personal information we have collected from you. There are a number of exceptions, however, which include but are not limited to when the information is necessary for us or a third party to do any of the following:
Complete your transaction;
Provide you a good or service;
Perform a contract between us and you;
Protect your security and prosecute those responsible for breaching it;
Fix systems in case of a bug;
Protect your free speech rights o or those of other customers;
Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et seq.);
Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interests that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws;
Comply with a legal obligation; or
Make other internal and lawful uses of the information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.
Other Rights. You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us due to your exercise of the rights provided by the CCPA.  We do not offer financial incentives or price and service differences, and we do not discriminate against consumers for exercising their rights under the CCPA.
Exercising Your California Privacy Rights. To request access to or deletion of your personal information, or to exercise any other rights under California law, please contact us using one of the following methods:
Website: You can use our Privacy Portal to exercise your privacy rights via our website.
Phone: You can call us toll-free at 1-800-513-0936
Email: You can email us to exercise rights. Please include your full name, email address, and phone number in your message, along with why you are writing, so that we can process your request in an efficient manner.
Response Timing. We aim to respond to a consumer requests for access or deletion within 45 days of receiving that request. If we require more time, we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.
Nevada Residents. Effective October 1, 2019, you may submit a verified request to us at privacy@johnstonmurphy.com to request that we not make any sale (as defined under Nevada law) of any covered information (as defined under Nevada law) that we have collected or will collect about you. We will respond to any such request as required by Nevada law.
If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy or this policy, or if you need to access this policy in another format, please contact us.
USE OF COOKIES
What is a cookie? A cookie is a piece of information that is sent to your computer's hard drive to help our site recognize you when you return to our site. Cookies are used as a standard practice by many sites. An example of how we use this function could be if you started to place items in your shopping cart, but then for some reason had to leave our site or shut off your computer. When you return to our site, the cookie would enable our site to recognize that you have returned and all the items you placed in your cart during an earlier session would still be in your shopping cart.
We also use cookies to determine the number of people that come to our site. It is important for us to understand the number of new customers using our site. When your computer accepts the cookie, we are able to record that session as a new visitor to our site. As important as cookies are to our site, we understand that this might make you uncomfortable. If you would prefer to not accept cookies from ours or any other site, you can modify the setting on your specific web browser to not accept them. Please refer to your browser's online help feature or the user's manual for instructions on how to do this.
Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
We also collect demographic and interest information via Google Analytics. Google Analytics is Google’s analytics tool that helps website and app owners to understand how their visitors engage with their properties. It may use a set of cookies to collect information and report website usage statistics without personally identifying individual visitors to Google. We provide website visitors the ability to prevent their data from being used by Google Analytics by opting out here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
DO NOT TRACK (DNT)
Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference you can set in most browsers. There is no standard interpretation or practice for responding to DNT signals. Therefore, we handle all user information consistent with this Privacy Policy. For more details, you can visit allaboutdnt.com” Currently, this site does not respond to DNT signals from your browser.
USER COMMENTS, FEEDBACK, POSTCARDS AND OTHER SUBMISSIONS
All comments, feedback, postcards, suggestions, ideas, and other submissions disclosed, submitted or offered to us on or by this Site or otherwise disclosed, submitted or offered in connection with your use of this Site (collectively, "Comments") shall be and remain Genesco's property. Such disclosure, submission or offer of any Comments shall constitute an assignment to Genesco of all worldwide rights, titles and interests in all copyrights and other intellectual properties in the Comments. Thus, Genesco will own exclusively all such rights, titles and interests and shall not be limited in any way in its use, commercial or otherwise, of any Comments. Genesco is and shall be under no obligation (1) to maintain any Comments in confidence; (2) to pay to user any compensation for any Comments; or (3) to respond to any user Comments. You agree that no Comments submitted by you to the Site will violate any right of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or proprietary right(s). You further agree that no Comments submitted by you to the Site will be or contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, abusive or obscene material. You are solely responsible for the content of any Comments you make. You agree that the Company may use and/or disclose information about your demographics and use of the Site in any manner that does not reveal your identity.
USER SUBMISSIONS
You may post or upload content you have created, including without limitation, photographs, your social media handle, videos, and comments (collectively, “User Submissions”) to your social media accounts. By posting and uploading User Submissions that you have tagged with #johnstonandmurphy or other Johnston & Murphy brand hashtags, you grant to Johnston & Murphy, its third-party service providers who provide content management services, and its retail partners (collectively, the “Licensed Parties”) the perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, fully-paid, non-exclusive, transferable right to use your Johnston & Murphy-tagged User Submissions in any manner to be determined in the Licensed Parties’ sole discretion, including but not limited to on their webpages, social media pages operated by Johnston & Murphy, and in other marketing, promotional and advertising initiatives, in any media now or hereafter known. The Licensed Parties may use, display, reproduce, distribute, transmit, create derivative works from, combine with other materials, alter and/or edit your User Submissions in any manner in their sole discretion, with no obligation to you whatsoever. You grant the Licensed Parties the right to use your username, real name, image, likeness, caption, location or other identifying information in connection with any use of your User Submissions. You hereby represent and warrant that (i) you own all rights in and to your User Submissions, (ii) you have permission from all person(s) appearing in your User Submissions to grant the rights granted herein; (iii) you are not a minor, and (iv) the Licensed Parties’ use of your User Submissions as described herein will not violate the rights of any third party or any law. You hereby release, discharge and agree to hold Johnston & Murphy, the Licensed Parties, and any person acting on Johnston & Murphy’s or their behalf harmless from any liability related in any way to the Licensed Parties’ use of your User Submissions.
COLORS
We have made every effort to display as accurately as possible the colors of our products that appear at the Site. However, as the actual colors you see will depend on your monitor, we cannot guarantee that your monitor's display of any color will be accurate.
NETWORK ADVERTISING
We use a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please click here.
We may from time to time contract with third-party vendors to work on our behalf to provide ads to our customers via the Internet or to send direct mail or catalogs to customers whom we think may be interested in our products or services. In order to do so, these third parties may collect information concerning visitors to our websites using JavaScript software code and “cookies.” A “cookie” is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser or mobile device by websites, mobile apps, and advertisements that you access or use.  This “cookie” is stored on your computer or mobile device and helps websites and mobile apps to remember things about you to improve your experience with the website.  Our vendors may then connect the information that they collect from our website using “cookies” to other sources of information, which may include your name and mailing address, for the purpose of sending you direct mail promotions. By using this site, you consent to these activities, including information collection by our vendors.  If you do not wish for cookies to be placed on your computer, most web browsers permit you to prevent that from taking place. Additionally, information about opting out of cookie-based advertising can be found via the following links - http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/ and https://www.neustar.biz/privacy/opt-out.  However, please keep in mind that cookies and similar technologies are an important part of how the website works; removing, rejecting, or limiting the use of cookies or other similar technologies might affect the availability and functionality of the website. To opt-out of receiving our direct mail or catalogs, you may send us an email at johnstonmurphy@johnstonmurphy.com or call us at 800.424.2854. We will honor those requests, but please understand that it may take 45 days for such mailings to end.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES
This Site may contain links to outside services and resources, the availability and content of which Genesco does not control. Any concerns regarding any such service or resource, or any link thereto, should be directed to the particular outside service or resource. The privacy policy, terms of use and other conditions of access specified on or applicable to any third party site will govern access and use of such site, the site owner's use of information obtained from users, etc.
SECURITY
Protecting your information is extremely important to us. We realize that prioritizing this issue will insure an exceptional shopping experience. To this end, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL encrypts all personal information including your credit card number, name, and address. With encryption in place, only Genesco can decode your information.
You can insure your connection is secure by looking in the lower left-hand corner of your browser window. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), the SSL is active and your connection is secure. Please note that SSL will not activate until you enter the login page after you have completed your shopping and are ready to check out.
You may also check your security level by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from 'http' to 'https.'
Please note that some versions of browsers don't permit communication even if the server is secure. This is also true of some firewalls. If for some reason you are unable to connect to our secure server or would rather place your order by phone, please call us at 800-424-2854. Orders may also be faxed to 800-654-2371.
DISCLAIMER
This site and all contents of the site are provided on an "as is" basis without warranties of any kind, either express or implied, including without limitation warranties of title or implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. You acknowledge, by your use of the site, that your use of the site is at your sole risk, that you assume full responsibility for all costs associated with all necessary servicing or repairs of any equipment you use in connection with your use of our site, and that the company shall not be liable for any damages of any kind related to your use of this site. This provision is unenforceable or inapplicable within the State of New Jersey.
INDEMNIFICATION
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold Genesco, its affiliates, subsidiaries, officers, directors, employees and agents harmless from and against any and all claims, damages, costs and expenses, including attorneys' fees, arising from or related to your use of the Site. This provision is unenforceable or inapplicable within the State of New Jersey.
MISCELLANEOUS
This Site is controlled and operated by Genesco from its offices in Nashville, Tennessee.
This Agreement shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee, without regard to any conflict of law provisions. Any dispute arising under this Agreement shall be resolved exclusively by the state and federal courts of the State of Tennessee, County of Davidson and/or the Middle District of Tennessee.
TERMINATION
This Agreement is effective unless and until terminated by either you or us. Either of us may terminate this Agreement at any time without notice.
To check your gift card balance, please enter the number and pin
found on the back of your gift card or in the E-Gift Card email you
received.
Gift Card Number
Gift Card Number
Gift Card Pin
Gift Card Pin
What is this?
The Pin is the 8-digit number that can be found under a scratch-off panel on the back of your gift card.
Check Balance
Gift Card Balance:
